## **Robert Stolyar**

6448 Geary Blvd, San Francisco, CA 94121

# Phone: (415) 812-5541 **Professional Summary:**

Email: rstolyar92@gmail.com

I have assisted many clients with support requests, issues and questions. Worked directly with customers on solutions, requirements for new features, bugs & feature improvements. Strong product, technical knowledge, communication and organizational skills. Demonstrated ability to work both independently and as part of the team. Talented at educating others on features of software.

### **Professional Experience:**

#### Customer Success, 2014 - 2018

(bitFit, Campbell, CA)

- Customer on-boarding, training, retention, growth, and satisfaction.
- Promoting a high level of adoption, customer health, and product usage.
- Creating customer heroes & advocates, and working proactively with marketing to tell their story.
- Created and delivered high-quality training on bitFit product features via webinars, group training sessions, and self service resources.
- Providing world class support desk services to the US customer base.
- Identified trends within support enquiries and creating efficiencies to proactively resolve them.
- Effectively collaborated & communicated with key internal stakeholders (such as sales, product, technology, solutions architects & marketing) to ensure continuous improvement for all support related matters.
- Reviewed emails/messages, phone calls, & Jira tickets.
- Replicated/validated any problems & resolved issues.
- Escalated issues to the product manager, & if we both couldn't resolve it it would get pushed to the developers where I prioritized tickets.

#### Quality Assurance, 2013 - 2014

(bitFit, Campbell, CA)

- Participated in test planning/estimation and create test cases to ensure requirements are met.
- Performed functional, regression, mobile and browser testing.

#### Tools:

• Jira, Slack, Google Suite. MS Suite

#### Education:

2013 - 2015 (San Francisco State University, San Francisco, CA) 2010 - 2013 (Skyline Community Junior College, San Bruno, CA)